androidapkmods.com 2018-05-29

# Android Apk Mods Privacy Policy | Android Apk Mods

Android Apk Mods.com is committed to protecting consumer privacy online. We believe that greater protection of personal privacy on the Web will not only protect our users, but also increase users confidence and ultimately their participation in online activities. The purpose of our policy is to inform you about the types of information we gather about you when you visit our site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of the information. Android Apk Mods.com strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. By using our site, you consent to our website’s privacy policy and [Terms of use](http://androidapkmods.com/terms-use# "Terms of use").

**1\. Cookies**  
We use “cookies.” The cookies we place on your computer are very small text files that uniquely identify your browser and may be sent to your computer or mobile device. They are stored on your hard drive and communicate with our servers only when you are visiting our websites. We use cookies to improve the quality of Android Apk Mods.com They allow us to monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and number of pages viewed. They also allow us to optimize Android Apk Mods.com to make sure that we are delivering the best possible experience to our users. Your web browser is likely already set to accept cookies, yet you may choose to block cookies in your web browser’s settings. Note that blocking cookies may result in some features not being able to function properly.

**2\. Device Information**  
We collect information regarding the Internet browser, computer, tablet, mobile phone, smartphone or other device utilized to access Android Apk Mods.com to ensure that Android Apk Mods.com is optimized for those devices.

**3\. Analytics**  
We use third party information, reports and analysis about the usage and browsing patterns of users of Android Apk Mods.com. We allow the third party analytics companies to include web beacons and cookies on Android Apk Mods.com. The collected information includes search terms, search parameters, click-throughs by users, and other similar information. We utilize this information to improve Android Apk Mods.com and make sure we are delivering relevant content to our users. The Analytics we use do not identify individual users of Android Apk Mods.com.

**4\. Log Files**  
We may also automatically log certain anonymous information about visitors to Android Apk Mods.com, including, but not limited to, where the user came from to visit our site, IP address, search terms utilized, browser type and a reading history of the pages viewed.

**Changes in Privacy Policy**

Android Apk Mods.com reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a notice at the Site explaining that we are changing our Privacy Policy.

**Contacting the Site**

This information is used to respond directly to your questions or comments. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us [here](http://androidapkmods.com/contact-us# "Contact Android Apk Mod") .

Last updated: December 23, 2017
